Guide to the Rice University Office of News and Media Relations videos, 1990-2008 UA 214
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Office of News and Media Relations videos collection
1990-2008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 214
6 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
The Rice University Office of News and Media Relations keeps the media and the institution's community informed about the latest campus developments. They research, develop and share press releases and record special events on video or audio. That charge led to this collection that consists mostly of VHS tapes which contain news broadcasts and raw footage covering Rice University events or featuring speakers representing Rice University on many topics.
Biographical / Historical
As the university's primary outlet for official statements and information, Rice University Office of News and Media Relations keeps the media and the institution's community informed about the latest campus developments. They research, develop and share press releases and record special events on video or audio.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists mostly of VHS tapes which contain news broadcasts and raw footage covering Rice University events or featuring speakers representing Rice University on various topics. Highlights include snipets on Nanotechnology and Nanotubes, The 2003 College World Series Championship, Terrorism, and International Affairs. Featured speakers include Amb. Edward P. Djerejian, James A. Baker III, Prof. Richard E. Smalley, Prof. Ric Stoll, Assoc. Professor Dan Wallach and Amy M. Jaffe, Associate Director of the Rice Energy Program. The collection also includes 20 VHS tapes of talks given at the James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy, 2000-2006.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to the Woodson Research Center in 2009.
Arrangement
This material is arranged in chronological order.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
All tapes are VHS videotape format except where noted at the end of Box 1.
Index Terms
Subjects
Rice University -- History; Nanotechnology; Universities and colleges
Document Types
videotapes
Subjects (Persons)
Smalley, Richard E.; Baker, James Addison; Djerejian, Edward P.
- VHS tapes, 1992-2002 and Non-VHS audio/video, 1990, 2000-2001, undated, 111986; 1 Linear Feet
  - Nightline 9/16/92 Rice University Dept of News and Pubs, 111992 (Box 1)
  - ABC Nightline 9/17/92, 111993 (Box 1)
  - "Earth Today" Grand Opening KPRC Ch.2 5pm & 6pm weather KNWS Ch.51 8pm news (Not for rebroadcast) 7/19/95, 111994 (Box 1)
  - Rice Nanoscience Fund raiser 10:30 5/31/96, 111995 (Box 1)
  - The Great Leveller 9/15/96, 111996 (Box 1)
  - President's lecture 9/24/97 Larry McMurtry "Manners at the Millenium and Beyond", 111997 (Box 1)
  - Modern Marvels: Future Tech CNST 6/24/98 Nanotech Rice Univ. tape# 24996, 111998 (Box 1)
  - Unedited footage IUB Press conference (12 Feb, 99) Provided by Radio Bremer TV, 111999 (Box 1)
  - Footage material – Bremen International University 8'43" 9/2/99, 112000 (Box 1)
  - CNBC tour – Sep 6, 1999, 112001 (Box 1)
  - Rice University 2:47 12/2/99, 112002 (Box 1)
  - Fire safety Ch.11 1/19/00 10pm news, 112003 (Box 1)
  - Modern Marvels: Future Tech Dr. Curl 4/10/00 Nanotech Rice Univ. tape# 24995, 112004 (Box 1)
  - Tomorrow's World Tx: 17/5/00 Janet Braam, Associate Professor of Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 112005 (Box 1)
  - July 6, 2000 Newshour with Jim Lehrer July 11, 2000 CNN July 16, 2000 CNN, 112006 (Box 1)
  - 60 minutes 9/10/00 McNeil Ch.11 9/14/00, 112007 (Box 1)
  - Levander, Students – Hill AFB Utah Air Force TV News Sep 18, 2000, 112008 (Box 1)
  - NHK Special Project 2000 – Episode 36 "Nanotechnology" 27th Sep, 2000, 112009 (Box 1)
  - Matali Bannerjet – voting 11/6/00 Ric Stoll – Baker 11/8/00 Earl Black 11/9 Brace 11/27 FOX, 112010 (Box 1)
  - ABC World News Tonight Ken Lay @ Rice Jan. 11, 2001, 112011 (Box 1)
  - Linda McNeil on CNN's Inside Politics Feb.20, 2001, 112012 (Box 1)
  - National Science Foundation America's Investment in the Future 3/2001, 112013 (Box 1)
  - Rice University Commencement May 12, 2001 Speaker: Morris Dees 3:00, 112014 (Box 1)
  - Prof. Bixby talks about flight delays 7/23/2001, 112015 (Box 1)
  - History Channel July 23, 2001 Gasoline – Amy Jaffe, 112016 (Box 1)
  - Earl Black on News Hour Jesse Helms 8/22/01, 112017 (Box 1)
  - Energy News Live 8/27/01 10am, 112018 (Box 1)
  - CNBC David Ikenberry 9/14/01, 112019 (Box 1)
  - Terrorism 10/3/01, 112020 (Box 1)
  - Rice Stoll on Fox (Bush's speech) EPD on CNN 10/11/01 Amy Jaffe on News Hour Pat Reiff 2/1 News 24, 112021 (Box 1)
  - 26, 13 Nov. 13, 2001 Greenspan, Putin – 13 6&10, 112022 (Box 1)
  - 39, 11 Nov. 13, 2001 Greenspan, 112023 (Box 1)
  - Greenspan, Putin coverage Nov 13-14, 2001, 112024 (Box 1)
  - Texas Children's Hospital – Latin American Symposium summary video 3:50 2001, 112025 (Box 1)
  - Media Training Kevin Ausman CBEN 8/21/02, 112026 (Box 1)
  - Non-VHS audio/video:, 112027 (Box 1)
    - Betacam: Rice University Commencement 5/13/90 B-roll no audio, 112028 (Box 1)
    - Rice University Commencement 5/13/2000 George Bush, former President, speaker (Sony tape), 112029 (Box 1)
    - Living.com: Hurdler 30; Kids; Psychc Rev. 30 (Sony tape), 112030 (Box 1)
    - "No Sound" (Sony tape), 112031 (Box 1)
    - Cassettes: Science update:, 112032 (Box 1)
      - Parallel computing 1/2000, 112033 (Box 1)
      - Insulin Implant 11/2000, 112034 (Box 1)
      - Artery Gel 12/2000, 112035 (Box 1)
      - Molecular Computer 12/2000, 112036 (Box 1)
      - Optimizing Airplanes 1/2001, 112037 (Box 1)
- VHS tapes, 2002-2003, 111987
  - Nightline Amb. Djerejian 4/3/02, 112038 (Box 2)
  - King of Jordan 13, CNN 5/9/02, 112039 (Box 2)
  - Ch.26 Wade Adams 6-8am May 23, 2002 NNI Workshop, 112040 (Box 2)
  - Vicki Colvin – Media coaching 7/16/02, 112041 (Box 2)
  - Nanotube Fluorescence Fox 26 news at nine 8/2/02, 112042 (Box 2)
  - Ch.26 9pm Nano Fluoresence 8/2 (circled), 8/3, 8/4 2002, 112043 (Box 2)
  - Ch.11 10pm Rice Police Aug 26, 2002, 112044 (Box 2)
  - Ric Stoll – Iraq Channel 39 Sep 8, 2002, 112045 (Box 2)
  - Ch.11 13 Shara 9/11/02, 112046 (Box 2)
  - Arthur Few – 9/24/02 Hurricane Isadore Ch. 48 Telemundo 5pm and 10pm news, 112047 (Box 2)
  - Predicting War 10/9/02, 112048 (Box 2)
  - Without Warning"–static fires at gas stations – Andy Brow 11/15/02 10pm, 112049 (Box 2)
  - CH. 26 – "Computer Drug Design – Lydia Karvaki; Ch.11-Visa Delays, Korisky and Si; Ch.11 – Tissue Engineering 11/25/02, 112050 (Box 2)
  - Rice University – Computer aided drug design – aired 11/25/02, 112051 (Box 2)
  - Rice in the news, Nov 25, 2002, 112052 (Box 2)
  - Newshour 12/17/02 Amy Jaffe, 112053 (Box 2)
  - Modern Marvels: Future Tech Rick Smalley energy 01/03 tape# 24997, 112054 (Box 2)
  - Ch.11 News – Jan 20, 2003 Halas, Lane, Wiesner, Kulinowski (MASTER), 112055 (Box 2)
  - RTC Installation B-Roll Jan 2003 (Courtesy Fox 26. Not for broadcast), 112056 (Box 2)
  - Djerejian CNN Blitzer 1/22/03, 112057 (Box 2)
  - Fox 26 – Jan 28, 2003– War Predictor Subramanian Stoll, 112058 (Box 2)
  - Amy Jaffe CNN 2/27/03, 112059 (Box 2)
  - CNN EPD Capital Gang 3/8/03 Wall Street Week 3/21, 112060 (Box 2)
  - EPD on Wolf Blitzer Reports (CNN) & News Hour with Jim Lehrer 3/14/03, 112061 (Box 2)
  - Ch.11 6pm Ric Stoll – Friendly Fire: Wade Adams Nano tech 3/31/03 (MASTER), 112062 (Box 2)
  - Ch.13 – Chemical Weapons – tour April 7, 2003, 112063 (Box 2)
  - 26 2 4/8/03, 112064 (Box 2)
  - Kyriacos Athanasion 4/11/03 Ch.11 Focus on Health Knee Miniscus (MASTER), 112065 (Box 2)
  - Ch.13 4/17/03, 112066 (Box 2)
  - Ch. 2 TSARP Conference TS Allison: Two Years Later May 8, 2003, 112067 (Box 2)
  - Ch.2 Small House May 22, 2003, 112068 (Box 2)
  - End of game channels 26, 39, 13, 2, 11 6/23/03, 112069 (Box 2)
  - Ch.2 One-hour special on Owls celebration 6/24/03, 112070 (Box 2)
  - Segways@Rice WB39 – July 2, 2003 9pm MASTER, 112071 (Box 2)
  - News 24 Houston – Halas DoD award – July 2003 MASTER, 112072 (Box 2)
  - Ch.11 Sept 16, 2003 RFID Tags – Patrick Fuantz-cmc (unattributed), 112073 (Box 2)
  - World News Tonight EPD Oct 6, 2003, 112074 (Box 2)
  - Newshour Oct 6, 2003 EPD, 112075 (Box 2)
  - CNN in the Money 10/11/03, 112076 (Box 2)
  - CHILL-Matt Fraser – Air Pollution Oct. 13, 2003, 112077 (Box 2)
  - 10th Anniversary Gala 10/17/03, 112078 (Box 2)
  - Newshour with Jim Lehrer 10/20/03 Smalley-Energy, 112079 (Box 2)
  - Ch.11 Oct 20, 2003 Nano Days 2003 – CBEN. Vicki Colvin, 112080 (Box 2)
  - Newshour w/Jim Lehrer Smalley energy 10/20/03, 112081 (Box 2)
  - Ch. 11 Nanotechnology 10/20/03, 112082 (Box 2)
  - "Bridging the Gap" – Science Poly Conf. Rice University – McMurtry Auditorium Levya Holdren Nov. 1, 2003, 112083 (Box 2)
  - Discovery Ch – Canada Nov. 2003 – Noami Hales Daily Planet, 112084 (Box 2)
  - Ch.11 Johnathan Walton in am Robin Foreman – big numbers Fall 2003, 112085 (Box 2)
  - Leebron press conf. 12/19/2003, 112086 (Box 2)
  - 24 – 2 stories 2-6pm 12/19/2003, 112087 (Box 2)
  - Medstar Source Nanoshells 44-03, 112088 (Box 2)
- VHS tapes, 2004-2005, 111988
  - Ch.13 Trafnen? 2/5/04, 112089 (Box 3)
  - 2, 26 2/10/04 Strippers, 112090 (Box 3)
  - Topless dancers – football parties Feb 10, 2004 Ch.2 (5,6pm) Ch.26….., 112091 (Box 3)
  - Ch.2 @ 5, 6, 10 Dan Wallach – estate w/Phil Archer (@5) 3/8/04, 112092 (Box 3)
  - 1)Ch.2 3/8/04 Phil Archer 2)CBS Evening News 3/10/04 3)Lou Dobbs 3/11/04 Dan Wallach regarding the security of electronic voting machines, 112093 (Box 3)
  - CBS Evening News 3/9/04 – Dan Wallach, 112094 (Box 3)
  - CNBC March 29,2004 5-8pm Vicki Colvin – Buckyball Toxicity (MASTER), 112095 (Box 3)
  - Scientific integrity in the Bush administration 4/7/04, 112096 (Box 3)
  - Mubarak 4/14/04 2/6pm 11/6pm 13/10pm 39/9pm 24/8pm 11/10pm 2/10pm 4/15/04 C-span 9:05pm, 112097 (Box 3)
  - Alhurra – Newshour EPD 4/15/04 (Box 3)
  - "Remembering Sadam" with paperwork April 2004, 112099 (Box 3)
  - Ch.2 news 10pm 5/3/04 Julia Morgan re TV movie "10.5", 112100 (Box 3)
  - Ch.2 10pm-Wallach and Bev Kaufman Phil A. (MASTER) May 15, 2004, 112101 (Box 3)
  - TOP Wallach on 2 talk shows 5/23/04 5/21/04 Athletics report Board decision, 112103 (Box 3)
  - BOTTOM Athletics report 5/21/04 MASTER, 112104 (Box 3)
  - Reagan photos at BIPP Ch.39 June 11, 2004, 112105 (Box 3)
  - Ch.39 news UofH Energy Conf. Wade Adams – CNL images June 15, 2004, 112106 (Box 3)
  - Ch.39 June 15, 2004 Wade Adams, 112107 (Box 2)
  - Ch.13 6pm – Texas lotto – June 16, 2004 Mike Wolf-Math(not named) MASTER, 112108 (Box 3)
  - Ch.26 – June 24, 2004 – Nano shells 1st animal trial Halas/West, 112109 (Box 3)
  - Ch.26 June 24, 2004 Nanoshells Animal Trial MASTER, 112110 (Box 3)
  - Ch.13 – NMR Install 800MHz 11am,4p,5pm,6pm – MASTER 6/30/04, 112111 (Box 3)
  - Ch.11 July 2004 – Walton's World – Oz Balloons MASTER, 112112 (Box 3)
  - Leebron 11-6pm 24- July 1, 2004, 112113 (Box 3)
  - Ch. 11 7/19/04 Holmes & Morris Ozone Balloons Shell Center MASTER, 112114 (Box 3)
  - "Will your vote count" CNN-Dan Wallach Master copy Aug 25, 2004, 112115 (Box 3)
  - Channel 8 Sept 28, 2004 Dan Wallach "The Connection" KUHT, 112116 (Box 3)
  - "Nano Cancer Fix" PUR 1228 uplink date 10/22/04, 112117 (Box 3)
  - Ch. 26 & 9 (World Series…oops!) Ch.11 @ 10 Lunar Eclipse 10/27/04, 112118 (Box 3)
  - Channel 2 10/27/04, 112119 (Box 3)
  - Ch.39@ 9 CH.13@ 10 10/27/04 Lunar Eclipse, 112120 (Box 3)
  - Ch.13 – Nov. 1, 2004 Dan Wallach, 112121 (Box 3)
  - CNN Arafat Amb. Djerejian / James Baker on Larry King 11/11/04, 112122 (Box 3)
  - Kathy Ensor – Ch.13 political polls following 2004 Democratic Nat. Conv. 6pm news, 112123 (Box 3)
  - Channel 39 12/21/04, 112124 (Box 3)
  - Ch.11 news 1)Tissue Engineering, tooth implants – Tony Mikes (5pm) 2)Sea Level change on the Tx Coast – John Anderson Dec. 2004, 112125 (Box 3)
  - Tony Ro: TMS Dr. Sean Kenniff – CBS News 2004, 112126 (Box 3)
  - CBS This Morning Sunday "Sate of Nano' by NYT editor David Pogue Nanokids taping at Spring Branch (not used) Jan 23, 2005, 112127 (Box 3)
  - TFA Wireless Channels 11 and 2 Feb 17, 2005, 112128 (Box 3)
  - TFA – Wireless Feb. 17, 2005 11-noon 2-4pm, 112129 (Box 3)
  - Shara Fryer in Focus: Foundations of Faith Michael Maas Mar 20, 2005 13, 112130 (Box 3)
  - Ch.26 Eden King – Obese Shoppers & Discrimination April 4, 2005, 112131 (Box 3)
  - Obese shopper study 4/18/05 Good Morning America 4/12/05 Fox News Channel 4/4/05 Ch.26 5/2/05 Ch.2, 112132 (Box 3)
  - Halas NOVA 4/19/05, 112133 (Box 3)
  - Fox News – May 2nd 2005 Smalley NASA Nanotube grant, 112134 (Box 3)
  - Bayaz toglu May 13, 2005 Ch.11 Williams commencement 5pm news MASTER, 112135 (Box 3)
  - Ch.2 10pm Vivian Ho May 14, 2005, 112136 (Box 3)
  - Ch.39 June 1, 2005 9pm Mike Wong Nano capsules MASTER, 112137 (Box 3)
  - Carter-Baker news conference 6/30/05, 112138 (Box 3)
  - Dan Wallach Ch.26 Aug 19, 2005, 112139 (Box 3)
  - 6pm Phil Bedient Katrina coverage What if a Cat 5 hit Houston 8/29/05, 112140 (Box 3)
  - Ch.2, 5pm Phil Bedient Sep 8, 2005, 112141 (Box 3)
  - Oct 17, 2005 Fox News Amb. Djerejian – Iraq's referendum 11/9/05 – Nightline, 112142 (Box 3)
- VHS tapes, 2006-undated, 111989
  - 2, 26 1/16/06 Shimon, 112143 (Box 4)
  - CNN Jan 7 2006 Fox Jan 8 CNBC Jan 17 Fox Jan 16 (IRAQ) Fox Feb 3, 2005, 112144 (Box 4)
  - Ch.13 Kyriacos Athanasiou Engineering Cartlage 2/16/06, 112145 (Box 4)
  - CNBC May 8, 2006 2pm Mackey CNN EPD May 9 9pm John King, 112146 (Box 4)
  - Azteca Ch.57 Matt Fraser@BP toxics 5/9/06, 112147 (Box 4)
  - 1)Ch.11 5pm Podcasts – Carlos Solis May 10, 2006 2) Ch.11 6pm Rice Biodiesel Project May 11, 2006, 112148 (Box 4)
  - CNN Situation Room – Wolf Blitzer Libya, etc. May 15, 2006, 112149 (Box 4)
  - 11/11am 26/noon 26/9-10 13/all times 9/27/06, 112150 (Box 4)
  - 2/11am 11/noon 2/4-5 11/5-6:30, 10-10:30 9/27/06, 112152 (Box 4)
  - Ch.2 5, 6 & 10 9/27/06 air toxics, 112153 (Box 4)
  - Shimon Peres 13, 39 - 1/16/07, 112154 (Box 4)
  - 2/14/07 Discovery Future Cave 2/27/07, 112155 (Box 4)
  - Severe storms 2006 Ch.2 news 3/15 6pm Ch.26 news 3/16 9pm, 112156 (Box 4)
  - Fox 26 June 8, 2007 Beyond traditional borders, 112157 (Box 4)
  - Chill – Connexions 8/28/08, 112158 (Box 4)
  - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology, 112159 (Box 4)
  - Amphibians: A Double Life (undated), 112160 (Box 4)
  - Ch.13 KTRK Ed Liang, 112161 (Box 4)
  - Ch.26 & Ch.2 Mars viewing – RSI observatory Chris Johns-Krull, 112162 (Box 4)
  - Ch.11 7 Ch.24 Mars viewings – RSI Observatory, 112163 (Box 4)
  - Ch.39, 13, 11 Mars viewings @ RSI observatory, 112164 (Box 4)
  - 3/10 CNN-Lou Dobbs-Dan Wallach – e-voting Bullseye w/Dylan Ratigan (MASTER), 112165 (Box 4)
  - Ch.11 – Feb 8 Climate change 10pm Nancy Holland Wiesner Hunt, 112166 (Box 4)
  - Ch.13 – TOP Ch.11 – BOTTOM, 112167 (Box 4)
  - Walton's World – Nanotube model, 112168 (Box 4)
  - Something Nobody Else Has (Turtles), 112169 (Box 4)
  - Science and Technology Conference (Honoring) Neal Lane Tape 1, 112170 (Box 4)
  - Science and Technology Conference (Honoring) Neal Lane Tape 2 (Box 4)
  - Science and Technology Conference (Honoring) Neal Lane Tape 3, 112172 (Box 4)
  - Science and Technology Conference (Honoring) Neal Lane Tape 4, 112173 (Box 4)
  - Modern Marvels: Future Tech Smalley tape #25000, 112174 (Box 4)
  - Modern Marvels: Future Tech Smalley – Chemistry Nobel tape# 25001, 112175 (Box 4)
  - Science for the rest of us demo Bruce Marcus, 112176 (Box 4)
  - Olson images for B-roll, 112177 (Box 4)
  - Rice University Rice Nanoscience fundraiser Window Burn, 112178 (Box 4)
  - Nanoscience animation: Bucky Balls, 112179 (Box 4)
  - Rice University, 112180 (Box 4)
  - Rice University program open/close generic Rice logo only Examples Only!, 112181 (Box 4)
  - EMBS IEEE – The Emerging Field of Biomedical Engineering, 112182 (Box 4)
  - Scientia Program #134 dub from master, 112183 (Box 4)
  - Scientia Program #43 dub from master, 112184 (Box 4)
  - Scientia Program #50 dub from master, 112185 (Box 4)
  - Smalley's death 10/28 MASTER, 112186 (Box 4)
  - Tape #2, 112187 (Box 4)
  - Tape #1, 112188 (Box 4)
  - 11 Stripper World News (Box 4)
  - Shara Fryer May 29, 30, 112190 (Box 4)
  - NYC High School counselors, 112191 (Box 4)
  - EPD on News Hour with Jim Lehrer, 112192 (Box 4)
  - CNN – Djerejian – terrorism, 112193 (Box 4)
  - Alberto Gonzales, 112194 (Box 4)
  - Treasurey Forum – Part 2, 112195 (Box 4)
  - unspecified, 112151
- VHS tapes, undated, 111990
  - Jade taping Ch.13 news Thurs March 9 lower vcr, 112196 (Box 5)
  - Ch. 2 10pm Dec. 23-25 Ric Stoll, protests Amy on Fox 10/23 Jerry Springer, 112197 (Box 5)
  - Shara Fryer May 22, 23, 26 6pm CNN May 27, 112198 (Box 5)
  - Crisis in America interview, 112199 (Box 5)
  - Treasury Forum on 39 WOE, EPD on 2 10/8, 112200 (Box 5)
  - Frontline 10/9/9? Mess in Iraq no BIPP mention, 112201 (Box 5)
  - Time & Presidency, 112202 (Box 5)
  - Shimon Peres, 112203 (Box 5)
  - Tom Brokaw, 112204 (Box 5)
  - Ric Stoll Ch.13 1/29 8 1/30, 112205 (Box 5)
  - Giuliani 1, 39, 112206 (Box 5)
  - Giuliani, 112207 (Box 5)
  - Giuliani 2, 26, 112208 (Box 5)
  - Fox March 8 7:15am, ABC March 8, 112209 (Box 5)
  - Leebron – Basketball – Jan. 28 10pm Ch.13, 112210 (Box 5)
  - Sept 9, 200? CNBC, 112211 (Box 5)
  - EPD Charlie Rose CNN Lou Dobbs Fox, 112212 (Box 5)
  - Fox 60 min, 112213 (Box 5)
  - Alan Greenspan @ Rice, 112214 (Box 5)
  - EPD compilation – Newshour, CNN, CNN w/Wolf Blitzer, Nightline, MSNBC………, 112215 (Box 5)
  - Nightline EPD, 112216 (Box 5)
  - MSNBC 52, 112217 (Box 5)
  - CNBC April 17, 5-6pm, 112218 (Box 5)
  - June 9 CNN 9pm EPD Carol Linn, 112219 (Box 5)
  - 13, 39 Putin, 112220 (Box 5)
  - 11, 26 Putin, 112221 (Box 5)
  - 11, 39 2&4 Jordan, 112222 (Box 5)
  - 13, 39 2/10 Strippers, 112223 (Box 5)
  - Berlin Wall Story – News 24 Oct. 2 Ch.11 Oct 1 5pm Also, Amb. Djerejian's report to Congress, 112224 (Box 5)
  - Jordan 2, 26, 112225 (Box 5)
  - Ch.11 Rice's cafeterias, 112226 (Box 5)
  - EPD on Charlie Rose, Fox News, Money line BIPP collection Amy on Lou Dobbs Steve on World News, 112227 (Box 5)
  - Scenes of Rice University, 112228 (Box 5)
  - Hatfield Oct. 30 – 11, 26 10:30, 112229 (Box 5)
  - Oct 14 Ch.26 6am Black Voices Noah Reiter – Rice EMS / Linda McNeil Ch.11 Nov. 20, 112230 (Box 5)
  - Biden, 112231 (Box 5)
  - Connection 7, 8, 112232 (Box 5)
  - Ch.11 Hubble, 112233 (Box 5)
  - Ch.11 Sunday Apr. 30 Lutige Bacteria powered Fuel Cells, 112234 (Box 5)
  - EPD CNN 4/9 MSNBC 4/14 MSNBC 4/15 CNN 4/16, 112235 (Box 5)
  - Djerejian middle east attack Oct. 12 CNN, Ch.26 12:30 39 9pm 2 10pm Oct 14 CNN, 112236 (Box 5)
  - Amy Jaffe 9/21 Ch.13 9/22 Ch.11, 112237 (Box 5)
  - 2, 11 CWS champs, 112238 (Box 5)
  - ESPN 26, 39, 26, 13, 112239 (Box 5)
  - Newshour with Jim Lehrer (McNeil); CNN (Djerejian); BBC Tomorrow's World (Braam)…, 112240 (Box 5)
  - National Geographic channel, 112241 (Box 5)
  - 12/22 Ch.2 Dale Sawyer 11-Texas plan, 112242 (Box 5)
  - Stoll, 112243 (Box 5)
  - Wall Street Week, 112244 (Box 5)
  - 4/10 Stoll 2 or 13, 112245 (Box 5)
  - 4/9 MSNBC, 112246 (Box 5)
  - C-Span 1 2/5, 112247 (Box 5)
- VHS tapes, James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy, 2000-2006, 111991
  - Dedication of the Berlin Wall Monument. Nov 10, 2000, 112252 (Box 6)
  - Mexico: The Policy and Politics of Modernization. HE Carlos Salinas de Gortari Mar 15, 2002, 112253 (Box 6)
  - Houston Task Force on Terrorism. Report. June 21, 2002, 112254 (Box 6)
  - The Ideas that Conquered the World: Peace, Democracy, and Free Markets. Michael Mandelbaum Jan 24, 2003, 112255 (Box 6)
  - U.S. Egyptian Relations and Opportunities and Challenges in the Middle East. Mubarak, El Baz, Zulficar, Ezz, Said Aly. Feb 3, 2003, 112256 (Box 6)
  - The Legacy of the Nurnberg Trials. Stein, Ference, Bass, Fowler, Morrow. Feb 12, 2003, 112257 (Box 6)
  - Baker Event. Media and Public Policy. Oct 18, 2003, 112258 (Box 6)
  - Globalism and Democracy. Amartyasen Nov. 11, 2003, 112259 (Box 6)
  - To the Moon and Back: Reflections on the Apollo Programme. John W. Young Dec. 8, 2003, 112260 (Box 6)
  - Enhancing Early Childhood Education and Development. Djerejian, Tarlov, Andres, Shattuck, Calaway, Musbacher, Graham. Jan 21, 2004, 112261 (Box 6)
  - His Excellency, Hosni Mubarak, President of the Arab Republic of Egypt Apr 14, 2004, 112262 (Box 6)
  - Anders Fogh Rasmussen, Prime Minister of the Kingdom of Denmark. Anders Fogh Rasmussen April 23, 2004, 112263 (Box 6)
  - The War on Terrorism After Iraq – Consequences for U.S. Domestic and Foreign Policy – Keynote. Robert M. Gates Dec 4, 2004, 112264 (Box 6)
  - Lecture by John Zogby May 9, 2005, 112265 (Box 6)
  - Saudi Arabia and the United States – Partners with Prosperity – The Energy Dimension. Abdullah S. Jum'ah May 16, 2005, 112266 (Box 6)
  - Perspectives on the United States Constitution panel Sep 16, 2005, 112267 (Box 6)
  - Suicide Attacks – Martyrdom Operations in the Contemporary Muslim World. David Cook. Oct 19, 2005, 112268 (Box 6)
  - Reaching for the Stars – Increasing the Role of Woman in Science and Engineering. Various Nov 7, 2005, 112269 (Box 6)
  - Reflections of an American Diplomat. Edward P. Djerejian. Feb 9, 2006, 112270 (Box 6)
  - Stem Cells – Saving Lives or Crossing Lines – Part II. Lessons Learned. Various. Mar 6, 2006, 112271 (Box 6)